fuze.com 2019-12-31

# Fuze Privacy Policy I Fuze

Effective as of 21 May 2018.

This “Privacy Policy” describes the privacy practices of Fuze, Inc. and our subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “Fuze”, “we”, “us”, or “our”). This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, disclose and otherwise process personal information in connection with our websites, mobile apps, and other services, and explains the rights and choices available to individuals with respect to their information. For convenience, our websites are referred to as the “Sites.” The Sites, together with our mobile apps and other services, are collectively referred to as the “Services.” This Privacy Policy applies to any of the Services on which the Privacy Policy is posted or linked. 

Individuals located in the European Economic Area should be sure to read the important information provided here. 

## Fuze’s Platform, Applications, and Customer Data

Fuze provides enterprise global voice, video, messaging, and collaboration software and applications that our customers use to communicate more effectively and efficiently (collectively, the “Fuze Platform”). This Privacy Policy does not apply to information processed during use of the Fuze Platform. Fuze customers have their own policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of their authorized users’ personal information, and Fuze is not responsible for our customers’ handling of such information. Our use of information processed during use of the Fuze Platform is restricted by our customer agreements. To learn about how a particular customer handles your personal information, we encourage you to read the customer’s privacy statement or contact the customer directly. 

## Personal Information We Collect

We collect personal information about you in the following ways: 

**Information you give us**

Personal information that you may provide through the Services or otherwise communicate with us includes: 

  * **Personal and business contact information,** such as your first name, last name, postal address, email address, telephone number, and company name; 
  * **Registration information,** such as your username and password;
  * **Feedback and correspondence,** such as information you provide in your responses to surveys and when you participate in market research activities, report a problem with the Sites, receive customer support or otherwise correspond with us; 
  * **Usage information,** such as information about how you use the Sites and interact with us; 
  * **Marketing information,** such as your preferences for receiving marketing communications and details about how you engage with them; and 
  * **Resume or CV information,** such as work experience, educational history, salary, and languages spoken. 

We may combine other publicly available information, such as information related to the organization for which you work, with the personal information that you provide to us through the Services. 

| 

## Information automatically collected

We may automatically log information about you and your computer or mobile device when you access our Sites. For example, we may log your computer or mobile device operating system name and version, manufacturer and model, browser type, browser language, screen resolution, information relating to how the Services function, your general geographic location derived through your IP address (e.g., your city, state, or metropolitan region), and the physical location of a device at the time of a crash, the website you visited before browsing to our Sites, pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, access times and information about your use of and actions on our Sites. We collect this information about you using cookies. Please refer to the Cookies and Similar Technologies section for more details. 

Our mobile app also includes various location-based features, such as connecting to the nearest Fuze data center to provide the highest quality of service. To provide location-based features, Fuze may collect, use, and disclose information about your general geographic location (e.g., your city, state, or metropolitan region). 

**Information from Social Networking Sites.** Our Site includes interfaces that allow you to connect with social networking sites (each a “ **SNS** ”). If you connect to a SNS through our Site you authorise us to access, use and store the information that you agreed the SNS could provide to us based on your settings on that SNS. We will access, use and store that information in accordance with this Notice. You can revoke our access to the information you provide in this way at any time by amending the appropriate settings from within your account settings on the applicable SNS. 

## Cookies and Similar Technologies 

**What are cookies?**

We may collect information using “cookies.” Cookies are small data files stored on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device by a website. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer or mobile device until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our Site. 

We use two broad categories of cookies: (1) first party cookies, served directly by us to your computer or mobile device, which we use to recognize your computer or mobile device when it revisits our Site; and (2) third party cookies, which are served by service providers on our Site, and can be used by such service providers to recognise your computer or mobile device when it visits other websites.

**Cookies we use**

Our Site uses the following types of cookies for the purposes set out below: 

Type of cookie | Purpose  
---|---  
Essential Cookies | These cookies are essential to provide you with services available through our Site and to enable you to use some of its features. Without these cookies, the services that you have asked for cannot be provided, and we only use these cookies to provide you with those services.   
Functionality Cookies | These cookies allow our Site to remember choices you make when you use our Site. The purpose of these cookies is to provide you with a more personal experience and to avoid you having to re-select your preferences every time you visit our Site.   
Analytics and Performance Cookies | These cookies are used to collect information about traffic to our Site and how users use our Site. The information gathered may include the number of visitors to our Site, the websites that referred them to our Site, the pages they visited on our Site, what time of day they visited our Site, whether they have visited our Site before, and other similar information. We use this information to help operate our Site more efficiently, to gather broad demographic information and to monitor the level of activity on our Site. We use Google Analytics for this purpose. Google Analytics uses its own cookies. It is only used to improve how our Site works. You can find out more information about Google Analytics cookies [here](https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies) and about how Google protects your data [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245). You can prevent the use of Google Analytics relating to your use of our Site by downloading and installing the browser plugin available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB).   
Targeted and advertising cookies | 

These cookies track your browsing habits to enable us to show advertising which is more likely to be of interest to you. These cookies use information about your browsing history to group you with other users who have similar interests. Based on that information, and with our permission, third party advertisers can place cookies to enable them to show advertisements which we think will be relevant to your interests while you are on third party websites. 

You can disable certain cookies which remember your browsing habits and target advertising at you by visiting: 

  * [Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada (DAAC) Consumer Choice ](http://www.youradchoices.ca/choices)(for Canadian users) 
  * [European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance (EDAA) Choice ](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)(for EU users) 

If you choose to remove targeted or advertising cookies, you will still see advertisements but they may not be relevant to you. Even if you do choose to remove cookies by the companies listed at the above link, not all companies that serve online behavioural advertising are included in this list, and so you may still receive some cookies and tailored adverts from companies that are not listed.  
  
**Disabling cookies**

You can typically remove or reject cookies via your browser settings. In order to do this, follow the instructions provided by your browser (usually located within the “settings,” “help” “tools” or “edit” facility). Many browsers are set to accept cookies until you change your settings. 

Further information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your computer or mobile device and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org.](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

If you do not accept our cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of our Site. For example, we may not be able to recognize your computer or mobile device and you may need to log in every time you visit our Site. 

**Pixel tags**

We may also use pixel tags (which are also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) on our Site to track the actions of users on our Site. Unlike cookies, which are stored on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device by a website, pixel tags are embedded invisibly on webpages. Pixel tags measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about usage of the Site, so that we can manage our content more effectively. The information we collect using pixel tags is not linked to our users’ personal data. 

**Do Not Track Signals**

Some Internet browsers may be configured to send "Do Not Track" signals to the online services that you visit. We currently do not respond to “do not track” signals. To find out more about "Do Not Track," please visit [http://www.allaboutdnt.com.](https://allaboutdnt.com/)

## How We Use Your Personal Information 

**To provide our Services and operate the Sites**

We use your personal information to: 

  * operate, maintain, administer, improve, and secure the Sites; 
  * study how the Sites are used and to improve the Sites and our other products and services; 
  * manage and communicate with you regarding your Fuze account, if you have one, including by sending you service announcements, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages; 
  * better understand your needs and interests, and personalize your experience with the Sites; 
  * provide support and maintenance for the Sites and our services; and 
  * respond to your service-related requests, questions and feedback. 

**To communicate with you**

If you request information from us, register on the Sites, or participate in our surveys, promotions or events, we will provide any requested information and may send you Fuze-related marketing communications as permitted by law. You will have the ability to opt out of such communications. 

**To comply with law**

We use your personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to comply with applicable laws, lawful requests and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities. 

**With your consent**

We may use or share your personal information with your consent, such as when you consent to let us post your testimonials or endorsements on our Sites, you instruct us to take a specific action with respect to your personal information, or you opt into third party marketing communications. 

**To create anonymous data for analytics**

We may create anonymous data from your personal information and other individuals whose personal information we collect. We make personal information into anonymous data by excluding information that makes the data personally identifiable to you, and use that anonymous data for our lawful business purposes. 

**For compliance, fraud prevention and safety**

We use your personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to (a) enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Service; (b) protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others; and (c) protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity. 

## How We Share your Personal Information 

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not share the personal information that you provide to us with other organizations. We disclose personal information to third parties under the following circumstances: 

  * **Affiliates.** We may disclose your personal information to our subsidiaries and corporate affiliates for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy. 
  * **Service Providers.** We may employ third party companies and individuals to administer and provide the Services on our behalf (such as customer support, hosting, email delivery and database management services). These third parties may use your information only as directed by Fuze and in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy, and are prohibited from using or disclosing your information for any other purpose. 
  * **Professional advisors.** We may disclose your personal information to professional advisors, such as lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers, where necessary in the course of the professional services that they render to us. 
  * **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement; Protection and Safety.  **Fuze may disclose information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as required by law, and disclose and use such information as we believe necessary or appropriate to (a) comply with applicable laws and lawful requests and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities; (b) enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Service; (d) protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others; and (e) protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity. 
  * **Business Transfers.** Fuze may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its business or assets, including your personal information, in connection with a business deal (or potential business deal) such as a merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy, in which case we will make reasonable efforts to require the recipient to honor this Privacy Policy. 

## Your Choices 

**Access, Update or Correct Your Information**

You may contact us at [privacy@fuze.com](mailto:privacy@fuze.com) to review, update or correct the personal information Fuze maintains about you in connection with your use of the Sites. 

**Marketing communications**

You may opt out of marketing-related emails by clicking on a link at the bottom of each such email, or by contacting us at [marketingreplies@fuze.com](mailto:marketingreplies@fuze.com). You may continue to receive service-related and other non-marketing emails. 

**Testimonials**

If you gave us consent to post a testimonial on our Sites, but wish to update or delete it, please [contact us.](https://www.fuze.com/contact)

## Choosing not to share your personal information 

Where we are required by law to collect your personal information, or where we need your personal information in order to provide the Services to you, if you do not provide this information when requested (or you later ask to delete it), we may not be able to provide you with the Services. We will tell you what information you must provide to receive the Services by designating it as required in the Services or through other appropriate means. 

## Security 

The security of your personal information is very important to us. We take a number of organizational, technical and physical measures designed to protect the personal information we collect, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no security safeguards are 100% secure and we cannot guarantee the security of your information. 

## International Transfer 

Fuze is headquartered in the United States and has affiliates and service providers in other countries, and your personal information may be transferred to the United States or other locations outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. 

European Union users should read the important information provided here about transfer of personal information outside of the European Economic Area. 

## Other Sites and Services 

The Sites may contain links to other websites and services. These links are not an endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites or services, and are not responsible for their actions. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of the other websites you visit and services you use. 

## User Generated Content 

We may make available on our Sites, or link to, features that allow you to share information online (e.g., on message boards, in chat areas, in file uploads, through events, etc.). Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online, that information becomes public and can be collected and used by others. We have no control over, and take no responsibility for, the use, storage or dissemination of such publicly-disclosed personal information. By posting personal information online in public forums, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy 

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy you will be notified via e-mail (where we have your contact information) or another manner through the Services that we believe reasonably likely to reach you (which may include posting a new privacy policy or a specific announcement on our Sites). 

Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon our posting of the new terms and/or upon implementation of the new changes on the Service (or as otherwise indicated at the time of posting). In all cases, your continued use of the Services after the posting of any modified Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the terms of the modified Privacy Policy. 

## Contact Us 

Email:

Address:

Fuze Privacy

2 Copley Place, Suite 7000

Boston, Massachusetts 02116 USA

If you live in the EU, you can contact our Data Protection Officer at: 

Email:

Address:

Fuze DPO c/o Jean-Philippe Prénovost,

133 Whitechapel High Street, London UK E1 7QA

## Additional Information for European Economic Area Users

**Personal information**

References to “personal information” in this Privacy Policy are equivalent to “personal data” governed by European data protection legislation. 

**Controller and Data Protection Officer**

Fuze, Inc. is generally the controller of your personal information for purposes of European data protection legislation. In some cases, the local affiliate with which you interact will be a data controller, either on its own or jointly with Fuze, Inc. Fuze’s EU representative for purposes of European data protection legislation is Fuze Europe B.V. For a list and contact information of local data controllers in the EU, including Fuze’s EU representative, click here. Our Data Protection Officer can be reached at [dpo@fuze.com](mailto:dpo@fuze.com). See the [Contact Us](https://www.fuze.com/contact) section above for additional contact details. 

**Legal bases for processing**

We only use your personal information as permitted by law. We are required to inform you of the legal bases of our processing of your personal information, which are described in the table below. If you have questions about the legal basis of how we process your personal information, contact us at [privacy@fuze.com](mailto:privacy@fuze.com). 

Processing purpose (click link for details) | Legal basis  
---|---  
To provide the Services | Processing is necessary to perform the contract governing our provision of the Services or to take steps that you request prior to signing up for the Services.   
To operate the Sites To communicate with you To create anonymous data for analytics For compliance, fraud prevention and safety To share your personal information (except where necessary to comply with law) | These processing activities constitute our legitimate interests. We make sure we consider and balance any potential impact on you (both positive and negative) and your rights before we process your personal information for our legitimate interests. We do not use your personal information for activities where our interests are overridden by the impact on you (unless we have your consent or are otherwise required or permitted to by law).   
To comply with law (including disclosure to third parties where legally required) | Processing is necessary to comply with our legal obligations.  
With your consent | Processing is based on your consent. Where we rely on your consent you have the right to withdraw it anytime in the manner indicated at the time we request your consent or by contacting us at [privacy@fuze.com.](mailto:privacy@fuze.com)  
  
**Retention**

We will only retain your personal information for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. 

To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of your personal information, the purposes for which we process your personal information and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements. 

Fuze retains information associated with an account for as long the account is active, or as long as the information is required to (a) provide you with the Services; (b) comply with our legal obligations; (c) resolve disputes; or (d) enforce our agreements. 

In some circumstances we may anonymize your personal information (so that it can no longer be associated with you) in which case we may use this information indefinitely without further notice to you. 

**Your rights**

European data protection laws give you certain rights regarding your personal information. You may ask us to take the following actions in relation to your personal information that we hold: 

  * **Opt-out.** Stop sending you direct marketing communications. You may continue to receive service-related and other non-marketing emails. 
  * **Access.** Provide you with information about our processing of your personal information and give you access to your personal information. 
  * **Correct.** Update or correct inaccuracies in your personal information.
  * **Delete.** Delete your personal information.
  * **Transfer.** Transfer a machine-readable copy of your personal information to you or a third party of your choice. 
  * **Restrict.** Restrict the processing of your personal information.
  * **Object.** Object to our reliance on our legitimate interests as the basis of our processing of your personal information that impacts your rights. 

You can submit these requests by email to [dpo@fuze.com](mailto:dpo@fuze.com) or our postal address provided above. We may request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and process your request. Applicable law may require or permit us to decline your request. If we decline your request, we will tell you why, subject to legal restrictions. If you would like to submit a complaint about our use of your personal information or response to your requests regarding your personal information, you may contact us as described above or submit a complaint to the data protection regulator in your jurisdiction. You can find your data protection regulator [here](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm). 

**Cross-Border Data Transfer**

Whenever we transfer your personal information out of the EEA to countries not deemed by the European Commission to provide an adequate level of personal information protection, the transfer will be based on one of the following safeguards recognized by the European Commission as providing adequate protection for personal information, where required by EU data protection legislation: 

  * Contracts approved by the European Commission which impose data protection obligations on the parties to the transfer. For further details, see European Commission Model contracts for the transfer of personal information to third countries. 
  * For transfers to recipients in the United States, ensuring they participate in the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework 

Please [contact us](https://www.fuze.com/contact) if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal information out of the EEA. 

## Fuze Corporate Entities / Data Controllers Covered by This Notice

Last Updated: 21 May 2018

1\. **United States:** Fuze, Inc., located at 2 Copley Place, Floor 7, Boston, MA 02116

2\. **Netherlands:** Fuze Europe B.V., located at Barbara Strozzilaan 201, Floor 5, 1083 HN Amsterdam

3\. **United Kingdom:** Fuze Europe (UK) Limited, located at One Valpy, 20 Valpy Street, Reading RG1 1AR
